Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living creature was harmed during
the production of this series
Do you want to dethrone Sultan Alaeddin...
...because he supported me?
You being against me means that
I am on the right way.
I will bring you death on your right way.
Give.
Stop!
-Nayman.
-Why?
While we are living in Bursa in peace..
Our enemies are making moves.
Right now, in Konya..
Osman is trying to enthrone Mesut who supports him.
Sir, Osman is daydreaming.
Konya is under the rule of Gazan Khan.
He can't do that.
Exactly, Commander Faustus.
Exactly.
The biggest mistake we can make..
Is looking down on our enemy.
Osman is thinking what you think.
A caravan from Tabriz, is moving
towards Konya right now.
Do not..
Ever feel let dusk fall on your hearts.
And answer me.
Are you ready to spill blood?
Our swords has waited enough
in their sheats, Lord Valens.
Today..
We will strike on four sides.
We will defeat all of his supporters.
While Osman is not here.
Who will we rain hell to, my Lord?
Those who live in tribes.
You.
You will march to Kizilbey Tribe.
You..
You will destroy Cavuldur Tribe
And you two..
You will destroy Demirkhan and Uraz.
Commander Faustus!
You will come with me.
We will destroy Osman's biggest legion together.
Today, rip down mercy from your heart.
The women of those sheep are also fighters.
Their children, hold grudges.
When they grow up, they seek revenge.
And elderly..
They are wise and experienced.
No mercy!
Let none alive.
Today, show no mercy for anyone.
No one will be taken captive, come on!
Osman.
This Bayindir and Mesut.
This treachery, can not be silenced.
This is a waste of time.
I manage a community, Nayman.
To not let this kind of treachery happen again..
I will behead them all to make an example.
I will skin this one.
They did a move..
And they received nothing in return except for failure.
I will hang their corpses for weeks in Konya.
That is, of course..
If Sultan allows it.
Why uncle?
Why?
You want this throne that much?
What throne are you talking about Alaaddin?
The only thing I wanted to interfere..
Is doing business with Nayman.
What about you, Osman Bey?
Is this your way?
To betray who raised you?
Sultan Alaeddin.
I grew up under the shadow of Seljuk State.
Because I grew up under its shadow..
I was a Bey worthy of traditions.
What about you?
You became blind as you grew up
under the shadow of Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan..
Neither sees..
nor shows truth to you.
Because of her hunger for power.
Truth you say?
Truth is what my eyes see.
There is no one but traitors in front of me right now.
You..
You've betrayed the Sultan of Seljuk State.
My mother asked
if I approved your death penalty.
My answer is..
Whatever Mother Sultan says.
Tomorrow, this will be done after the sun rises.
Take them away!
Until Osman's head is cut off...
No one will enter Konya, Bendu.
We put Osman in the cage.
He will lose his head soon.
Why are you worried, Commander Nayman?
We put the sheep in the cage...
...but we will not stop being careful.
Until Osman's head is cut off..
...I will have the east and the west in my hands.
You will hold the east, Bendu.
Gazan Khan might make a move to weaken...
...the people in Konya.
If he makes a move..
...we will crush them before arriving in Konya.
Come on.
Celali! You know your limits, right?
I do, my Sultan.
That's why you lived for so long.
That's why you served Konya for all your life.
Those who know their limits live long.
But that Osman never knew his limits.
Mother Sultan...
Forgive me, but..
...why didn't we kill him there?
Unfortunately...
...Osman has a reputation among Turkmens.
If he does not die next to Mesud...
...his treason cannot be proven.
Thus..
...there won't be a silent death.
His death will teach a lesson to everyone.
It will, so his dead body...
...will be announced as a traitor.
Soldiers!
Celali.
But there is such a person that...
..he won't die easily.
Until I get rid of my anger...
...you will not stop, Celali.
At the beginning, we were on the wrong way.
But we fell on the right way.
Being forgiven by you..
.means nothing to me.
May Allah forgive this poor man.
You were with me when I was playing all those...
..games..
Do you think you are on the right way just because you...
...stood against me in one of those games, Bayindir?
No.
Not everyone who looks for it cannot find it...
...but everyone who found it must have looked for it at one point.
I did not tell you that I reached the right way.
I said I fell on the right way.
Ismihan Hatun.
I will not hear anything but his screams of...
..pain, Celali.
Take him!
We failed, huh, Osman Bey?
Who said that, Sultan Mesud?
We have not lost yet.
You would not make a move before planning
a game in another game, my Bey.
Osman Bey...
We are already miserable in this dungeon.
Do not lock us in our curiosity.
Unfortunately, Konya is under
Gazan Khan's control.
Unless we receive an order
or a will from him...
...your throne will not be rightful.
I told Gazan Khan that Nayman
and Ismihan are working together...
...and that they are trying to drag
Sultan Alaeddin into the game.
Sheikh Edebali and Turgut
went to Tabriz for this.
Gazan Khan will send a troop
and take us out of here.
If Allah permits, he will let you
sit on the throne of Konya.
Osman Bey...
You planned your move with details again.
You did that, but...
...what if that army cannot
arrive in Konya?
My Bey...
Do we depend on the army that Gazan will send?
What if they cannot arrive on time?
What are we going to do then, my Bey?
Then we will come together with the ultimate ending.
We will drink the sherbet of shahada.
But no... We won't die easily.
We have valiants like Salancu and Korkmaz,
although they are not crowded.
Now... They will give us swords.
And we will fight at the risk of our lives.
Thank you.
You are coming with us, Osman Bey.
Where is Osman Bey going, brother?
can come.
-Alps, wait.
Wait. Come here.
Come here.
There is no need to be worried.
Be careful.
We will either succeed or die.
We've made good money recently.
We'll racketeer much more.
Where are we going next?
We'll visit all the villages
around to racketeer.
Our pouches will be full of coins.
Come on.
Folks!
You've filled your stomachs.
You can't leave without paying.
Look at him! He's talking to us!
Be grateful that we didn't kill you.
Buzz off!
If you don't pay, don't come here again!
No food for free!
Maybe I will, maybe I won't.
It's none of your business!
Your mouth is too big for an innkeeper.
Let's take care of that.
Leave my son! Just get out of here.
Leave the boy.
ForumKayi.com
Gazan Khan's commander.
You are Esrigun Banu.
Bala Hatun,
...daughter of Sheikh Edebali,
wife of Osman Bey.
I heard your reputation
from your father Sheikh Edebali.
-He sent salaam for you.
-Aleykum selam.
Did they know who you are?
In usual stories, heroes save
the innkeeper's daughter.
I saved the innkeeper's son today.
You've rested long enough!
We came here to solve a problem.
We can go now.
Come on, Sisters! Tell the alps
to prepare the wagons.
May Allah's greetings be upon you.
O The Most Generous!
O my Merciful Allah!
My Allah..
I've come to You.
The cruel keep tyrannizing.
The darkness keeps living in dungeons.
But...
But Your light is eternal, my Allah.
Your Mercy is eternal, my Allah.
Allah.
Save me from this darkness, my Allah.
You have all the belongings and the sovereignty.
My cause is being away from the evil and wrong.
My only cause is spreading..
...the words of Quran in the whole world.
My Allah, help me get rid of...
...all the obstacles against my cause.
My Allah, let me and my kin..
..be servants of Islam.
Accept my prayers, my Allah.
We equipped Konya like
an impassable army, Mother Sultan.
And we placed the loyal soldiers...
...in the secret passages as you ordered.
And we laid traps in the passages
as a precaution.
If anyone comes through those passages,
...it will be their graves!
What about soldiers?
Did they mingle with the people?
Yes, Mother Sultan.
In case of an attack they will agitate...
...and make the people attack all together.
Good.
Neither a sword nor
a commander can capture...
...a city that has become
a whole with its people.
What are we taking measures against, Mother Sultan?
Won't you let us know?
Measures are always required, Celali.
Both Mesud and Osman will be beheaded.
I will show my power to the whole world...
So if anyone makes a move to save them,
...I will destroy their courage.
Until Mesud's head falls down
...you will always be with my Sultan son, Celali.
Some will intend to leave the palace without
a Sultan and Konya without a head.
You will drown them in their own blood.
Now let's go..
...and talk to my Sultan son before
the executions tomorrow.
Sultan Alaaddin isn't in his chamber.
Where is he?
What is it, Mighty Sultan?
You wanted to see your servant
Osman in the dungeon?
Neither I see Osman as my servant...
...nor does Osman accept me as a Sultan.
You're just a traitor, Osman.
Mighty Sultan..
The state isn't ruled by you..
..but by Mother Sultan.
All the soldiers obey her.
But you are just ignoring that.
I can't serve that.
And what is so-called traitor Nayman doing?
He's protecting my throne.
And fighting against the rioters within the state.
Supposedly, Nayman is the enemy.
And what about you? An ally, Osman?
Mighty Sultan!
I'm the enemy of everyone
who is against Turks and Islam.
But..
You claim I'm a rioter.
So tell me..
What did I riot against?
Against me, Osman!
Sultan Alaaddin.
I have no hostility against you.
But you are ignoring
Mother Sultan's evil games.
Tell me...
How did you ascend the throne?
Are you questioning the legitimacy
of my sultanate now?
Sultan Mesud wanted to make Konya free.
He wanted to break Mongolians.
But Mongolians...
...wanted a Sultan who would do
whatever they wanted.
So Mother Sultan made
a deal with Mongolians.
That's how you ascended the throne,
Mighty Sultan.
Tell me.
What did you do...
..for the cause of Turks?
What's the cause of Turks?
My cause is the freedom cause of Turks.
If Konya is to be taken captured,
...then the frontiers will remain free.
If Konya is to be crushed,
...then the frontiers will rise.
If one hand leaves the flag,
..the other hand will carry it.
That's how we've existed so far.
And so will we forever.
YENI SEHIR
OSMAN BEY'S MANSION
Do you know what threw Hadrat Ibrahim to fire?
Because he broke the idols, Kumral Abdal.
No.
Because he didn't prostrate to Nimrod.
That Nimrod...
...saw himself as the God of his people.
When they took...
...Hadrat Ibrahim to him with
the crime of breaking the idols...
...Nimrod wanted him to prostrate.
When Hadrat Ibrahim told Nimrod that...
..."I swear that I will not prostrate to...
...anyone but my Creator
who created you and me...
...and all the worlds"...
he showed his side.
Maybe he would forgive what was done to the idols,
but the greatest idol was Nimrod's nafs (self).
Hadrat Ibrahim hit Nimrod's nafs...
...with his toughest sword.
Nimrod was so panicked that...
so panicked that...
in front of his people...
his nafs was damaged so heavily that...
He said "start a fire right away!"
Start a vast fire
that has never seen before.
A fire to burn Hadrat Ibrahim!
A huge fire!
If Hadrat Ibrahim...
had turned away from the path of Haqq
and prostrated to Nimrod,
that fire wouldn't have been set.
But how could he?
Is it possible to turn away from Haqq
for people like Nimrod?
No.
Of course not.
Ibrahim knocked all the idols down.
Ibrahim screamed
"I don't like the ones that sink away"
"I accept no Creator but the One
that is Eternal and Infinite".
And he walked towards the fire
that Nimrod started...
...without a shadow of fear in his heart.
Do you know why?
He knew that the fire
wouldn't burn him.
This is how you become Ibrahim.
Nimrod's fire is torture
and Ibrahim is the justice
that is not burnt in that fire.
Justice is gold.
No matter how big the fire of cruelty is...
...no matter how fierce it is...
...gold will still be the same gold.
It only clears away the dirt.
We should...
...be gold as Ibrahim,
free from all the dirts...
so that the fire of Nimrods
cannot find anything to burn
inside us.
Sultan Alaeddin.
Nayman keeps setting up his tricks.
But...
...but you cannot see it.
As you can't...
...carrying this banner
is beyond your ability.
How dare you?
You think that Konya
cannot hold the banner, is that so?
You can't because you
side with the enemy...
and damage Turks.
You are not seeing the truth, mighty Sultan.
Nayman..
...wants to cooperate
with the Lord of Bursa.
First he will raid the Frontiers.
And then he will move towards Konya, but...
...but you will not be able to see it.
Do you have a proof?
I don't need proof.
Don't worry.
I will not let it happen.
Even if what you said is true...
...You will not be able to
stop any of them, Osman.
I will.
You will be executed today.
Hadrat Sultan.
Are we in Mongol lands
that you are trying to break us?
This is the price of rebellion!
The throne will eventually be mine.
Konya will break the chains of Mongols.
Let him deal with the Lord of Bursa.
I will put an end to all of them in no time.
When I had never dropped the Turkish banner,
you shouldn't have tried to take
the banner from me, Osman.
One of your hands is with the enemy
and the other one holds the banner.
This is not right, mighty Sultan.
This does not suit the cause of Turks.
Slowly, Huseyin, slowly.
This is my life.
Where is my Osman Bey brother?
Tell me!
Where did you take my Bey?
Just wait for us to leave, then I'll tear off your hearts!
I'll cut your
tongues one by one!
We shouldn't have left my Bey,
The Mother must have a move.
Or why would she take my Bey?
If they attempt anything evil, I'll turn Konya into a hell for them.
Are you ready for martyrdom, brave boys?
-Tell me brother, who are you?
-We are loyal to Commander Korkmaz.
We pledged to Sultan Mesut.
Thank you, valiants.
Our state will be saved
thanks to the soldiers like you.
Tell me brother, where is my Osman Bey?
They threw him into the dungeon,
that's all we know.
Commander Nayman.
Come on in.
Our scouts heard that a group of people
came from Tebriz, great Nayman.
Who?
Who is that man that I will kill?
I don't know Commander Nayman.
Soldiers are looking for them.
That group shall never reach Konya.
Osman will lose his head.
Only I will rule in Konya.
No one will stop this.
I don't want any incompetency.
I want the heads of those people.
Come on!
No one whose head is on his shoulders...
...will arrive in Konya.
Kill everyone!
Do not show mercy to anyone.
Soldiers! Attack!
Protect the Princess!
Your end has come, Princess.
Soldiers! Trap! Run!
They are running!
So it is time.
If you allow me, before I set out...
-Don't worry, Bengi.
I know what you are going to say.
We are not setting out now.
We will first go to your tribe...
...so you can ask for your people's pardon.
There is no need for that, Bengi Hatun.
No... They should tie them.
They should tie them, so I can be punished.
Tie them..
...so my greed which I could not
defeat will be slapped again.
Tie them.
Your conscience is making you
suffer the most, Bengi.
There is no need for further punishment.
Come on. Let's go.
Our children are waiting for us.
I wanted to kill you like a soldier...
..in the battlefield.
But...
you chose dying like a traitor.
You think one can only fight in the battlefield.
That's why you will lose in the end.
Those are brave sentences for a person...
...who will lose his head soon, Osman.
You lost.
Only Allah knows that.
Those shameless men
who betrayed the state of Seljuk...
...will die here today.
They wanted to dethrone Sultan Alaeddin...
...and replace him with..
..Mesud, who cannot even..
...help himself.
They deceived our Commanders!
No one should keep treason in their hearts!
Those who betray...
...will die like them.
First, the leader of the traitors...
...who spread the fire of rebellion...
...and will die with his sins....
...Osman Bey.
Our desire to fight...
..was never against the state of Seljuk.
We were against the ones
who worked with the cruel.
O, people!
Do not forget who allied
with that cruel Nayman.
Do not forget how they oppressed us.
For every drop of blood that was shed,
flare up the fire of revenge.
Because..
..when we fall..
..you will stand up.
-Kill him now!
-Stop there.
I bear witness that there is no deity but Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammed
(PBUH) is His servant and His Messenger.
Bala!
My Osman!
Esrigun..
Nayman must be holding the ways.
You will bring Princess Esrigun to Kartalsuyu.
And we will get rid of those soldiers
and join you.
Who are you?
Gazan Khan's adopted daughter...
...and his most talented Commander...
Whoever you are..
...you cannot come into Konya's palace...
...without an allowance and with a traitor by your side!
Konya is the property of Gazan Khan, Ismihan.
And Osman Bey...
...is Gazan Khan's friend.
Your soldiers should sharpen
their swords, Faustus.
We're close.
We sharpened our swords
with our anger, my Lord.
We will show no mercy to Turks.
Good.
We will destroy all who support Osman.
If Osman succeeds in Konya..
He will not find anyone capable of
fighting when he comes here.
My Lord, you still haven't told us
where we're attacking.
We will attack Kargin Tribe.
We will destroy who comes before us.
Konya is a state of Islam.
It seems Osman Bey has sent a letter.
I confirm the letter.
However..
Instead of Sultan, his mother speaks.
Nayman, who rebelled and became a Khan, is also here.
Palace of Konya will be your tomb,
you arrogant Hatun!
To you as well, Bala Hatun.
Mother Sultan.
Surrender.
So no more blood would be shed.
Valiants!
Swords!
Ya Allah!
You will stop making coins for now.
Osman Bey will tell you what to do, after he arrives.
As you command, Malhun Hatun.
Malhun Hatun! Malhun Hatun!
What is it Gokluce?
What happened?
Bursa's Lord has attacked in four sides.
What are you saying?
Tribes send words.
Uraz Bey, Demirhan Bey, all sent words.
It is not good.
Valiants, ready horses!
One group is also heading Karkin.
Orhan, Alaeddin come on we're leaving.
Ulgen, send word to Kumral Abdal.
Send word to all healers everyone to tribes.
Gokluce, Inegol, Bilecik, Karacahisar..
Send word to everywhere, tell them to be cautious.
Come on my children.
Ismihan.
If Esrigun is here, then Konya wants me to bow down.
Konya still belongs to Gazan, Ismihan.
We need to step back.
Konya is mine.
I will die but not surrender it, Nayman.
We will go now, to be able to take back Konya
Celali, protect the Sultan.
-Osman, they're escaping!
-Let them go.
Their time has come,
Mesut has the throne now.
My Cicek Hatun?
Why are you staring all innocent?
I'm good.
I'm very good.
What will I do without my mother, Aktemur?
My father left, my sister Esra left.
Now my mother goes.
My Cicek.
I'm here.
I will not go anywhere, always by your side.
Two years pass by quickly.
It's not like she cannot come back.
This separation will end one day.
Aktemur, promise me.
Promise me to not leave me.
How can I leave you, my Hatun.
I promise.
Aktemur's promise.
Are we allowed in, Bey?
Come, Kutlu.
Bey, Bengi Hatun is here.
My mother is here, Aktemur.
Thank you.
You go quickly to follow Osman Bey's order.
As you command, Bey.
Let's go.
Welcome, Bengi Hatun.
-Welcome.
-Mother!
Welcome.
I hope it will be a short separation,
Mother Bengi
Aybars?
-What's this?
-I don't know my Bey.
Take a look.
Careful!
We will make Turks experience hell.
Hold the gates!
Attack!
Alcicek, gather the women and children at the back.
Protect them, come on!
-Come on, this way!
-Give me a sword, come on!
We will show no mercy today!
We will not spare them!
Gazan Khan wants you to sit on the throne.
Thank you Osman Bey.
Thank you too, mighty Sultan.
Esrigun Hatun, you came right on time.
Thank you.
You have been fighting alone against the traitor
who rebelled against us, Osman Bey.
We are actually late.
Now...
...we will talk in private with Osman Bey.
Osman Bey.
Come with me.
We sat on this throne thanks to Gazan Khan.
This throne is useless now.
The one that gives meaning to a throne
is the one who takes it.
Mighty Sultan,
we know very well how well-intended you are.
It does not matter.
Both throne and the one who sits on it are useless.
What are you trying to say, my Sultan?
The one who stays in the shadow cannot blossom, Osman Bey.
No matter how hard I try, it won't.
Konya will die under the shadow of Mongols.
The old tree...
...must break its dry branch...
...so that the sprout can see the sun.
We are from the same root.
We want to grow and blossom.
Osman Bey,
From now on, Konya will struggle
for you to see the sun.
-Mighty Sultan...
-This is the truth, Osman Bey.
The soldiers, catapults and all the guns
that I promised to you will
set out as soon as possible.
Konya does not need this power anymore.
And it has no power to use them.
Will you hand over the banner to me?
You have been holding the banner
for a long time Osman Bey.
The eyes hardly see it.
The tongue hardly speak it and
the heart hardly believe it.
Mighty Sultan.
I swear that I will make Turks free.
I will raise generations that will make
Turks rule the world.
I swear that
I will plant our banner to the highest
place of this world.
Your oath is my oath, Osman Bey.
Have a safe journey.
My Sultan.
The path of the The Red Apple
is always open.
- May you live long.
- Thank you.
Stop!
This is the end for you.
Byzantine is Great.
You are just shepherds.
You can't get away with this.
You will pay for this!
Alcicek!
-Mother! Mother!
-Alcicek!
Mother!
Alcicek..
Mother! Let go of me!
Aktemur!
This is the fate of people who stands against us!
Aktemur! Leave me!
You should feel lucky that you're
one of the first to die.
Leave me!
Aktemur!
Aktemur! Aktemur!
Leave me! Aktemur!
Leave me!
Put them all in the tent!
Aktemur!
-Burn them alive!
-Alcicek...
Aktemur!
-Aktemur!
-Shut up.
Aktemur!
-Both you and your mother are dead.
-Aktemur!
Divine justice.
Leave me!
No mercy today!
No forgiveness today!
ForumKayi.com
Help! Help!
Calm down. I'll save you.
We will be alright.
Help!
Save us! Help!
Come here! Don't get close to the fire.
Aktemur.
Help!
Alright, kids. We'll be alright.
Calm down.
-Help!
-Help us, my Allah.
Save us, my Allah.
Aktemu
Aktemur!
Mother!
Aktemur! Aktemur!
-Aktemur!
-Mother...
Alcicek... Kids.
-Help! Help!
-Help us!
Aktemur.
Alright.
Aktemur?
Aktemur, wake up!
Aktemur, wake up! Open your eyes!
Alps, come on
Help the injured!
Aktemur! Aktemur!
-Aktemur!
-Malhun.
Malhun, Alcicek is burning!
Save her! She's burning!
-Save Alcicek!
-Where is she?
There! Come on! Save Alcicek!
Come on! Go, hurry up!
Alps, put out the fire!
Put it out! Alcicek!
Alcicek, hold on! Alps!
Alps, put it out!
Bring water! Alcicek!
Come on, put it out! Come on!
Come on! Alcicek!
-Put it out!
-Come on, faster!
Oh my dear..
Aktemur!
-Calm down.
-Aktemur...
Is he dead? Is he dead?
Is he dead?
Is my son dead? Tell me the truth.
He's dead.
Aktemur! Don't leave me. Aktemur!
Aktemur! Stay here.
Aktemur, stand up! Come on!
Aktemur! Aktemur, stand up!
Put it out, come on.
There are kids. Kids!
Come on, kids.
Take the kids away!
Come on.
Alcicek? Alcicek.
Alcicek, come on.
Aktemur... Aktemur!
-Alcicek.
-Aktemur!
Aktemur... Aktemur! Aktemur!
Aktemur!
My dear.
Ayse, alright. Calm down.
-Malhun, my son is dead.
-He'll survive.
Alps, bring the stretcher!
Ayse, Ayse.
-Come on!
-He's breathing.
-Yes.
-He's breathing!
-Come on!
Come on, alps!
Carry Aktemur inside! Come on!
-Carry him inside!
-Hold him.
-Come on, take him.
-Alps!
Come on.
If Allah permits, we'll have arrived in Yenisehir
before dark.
And Sultan Mesud's aids..
...will come after us, I hope.
When Sultan Mesud ascended
the throne we both got what we wanted...
...and saved Konya from the clutches of traitors, my Bey.
Yes, Bala.
But you still have some doubt.
Yes. Ismihan's escape, my Bey.
I won't feel at ease before I see her caught.
You're right.
But she has nowhere to go.
This is the end for her.
Yet..
What makes me worried is..
...what the Lord of Bursa did while
we were fighting in Konya.
He sees us as enemies, after all.
He'll make a move.
My Bey! My Bey!
My Bey!
Kargin Tribe...
Lord Valens attacked Kargin Tribe
and the other tribes.
What are you saying?
What's the situation?
It's not good at all, my Bey.
Mother Sultan will flee to the enemy's land now.
Send alps all around.
We're going to Kargin Tribe.
Come on, alps!
Where are the scouts, Faustus?
They'll be here shortly, sir.
I can't let Konya gain power
with barbarians again.
The fate of these lands..
...will be determined by Christ's
loyal servants.
What will we do, sir?
Attack Konya?
I'll stick to my
alliance with Konya.
Whoever stands against us...
...is doomed to be destroyed, Leo.
But,
first we need to find out
what's happening in Konya.
Where are the scouts, Faustus?
Sir.
Lord Valens.
As Osman Bey and others were getting executed,
the Mongolian Princess stopped the execution.
Sir, they put Mesut on the throne
with the order of Gazan Khan.
I swear by Jesus that
I'll exterminate them.
What about Nayman?
Where is he?
They drew back to the Frontiers with
Mother Sultan and Sultan Alaeddin, sir.
Nayman withdrew, so are we going to
oppose Gazan Khan, sir?
-Faustus.
-Yes sir.
Go to the Frontiers
and find Nayman.
Right away sir.
Leo, get the soldiers ready.
We will go to Konya.
Ya Shafi (The Curer).
He will be all right, right mother?
He will be all right?
His wound is so deep, girl.
He has lost a lot of blood.
But my son is strong.
He will get up, right, Kumral Abdal?
If Allah permits.
Hatuns.
You also have a lot of injuries,
come here and let us take a look.
I'm all right, I don't want it.
You cannot help anyone in this condition.
There are injuries all around.
Bengi, Ayes, pull yourself together.
Mother.
We have put out the fire.
Healers are dealing with the injured ones.
Martyrs are ready to be buried.
All right my children.
I died.
I couldn't protect him.
I couldn't protect my trust.
I lost my Oktem
I lost my tribe.
I'm dead now.
You promised me.
You told me that you wouldn't leave me alone.
Come on, hang on!
It's all my fault.
My children are paying
for my sins.
Ulgen, bring me water with
vinegar right away!
Quickly!
He's burning.
Nayman's Base
Osman's plan annulled the seal, Nayman.
Did you trust this one?
You are the Sultan of Konya, Alaeddin.
Sultan.
The fact that Gazan overshadowed your reputation
is no one's business.
It is time to think in silent.
Osman...
Gazan Khan and Beys...
...are with Mesut.
We need a great power
that will break this down.
Great Lord of Byzantium.
Valens is our ally.
He has a strong army behind him.
Great Nayman, Lord Valens
attacked Turkmen tribes.
Kargin tribe was among them.
Our enemy and our hostility is the same.
It is my turn, Nayman.
I will use the power of Sultan.
I will gather brave warriors
who seek revenge
behind me.
How?
I'll leave with my son now.
Soon,
I will come back with
blood-thirsty soldiers.
It says 400 swords here
I promised 1000 swords to Osman Bey.
Do you want them to say Sultan is
on the throne but he cannot keep his promise?
Get out!
It is important than ever before.
Melt all the irons and helmets of the soldiers...
...then complete the missing swords
and send them away.
Yes my Sultan.
What about the troops that will leave?
-They are getting ready, my Sultan.
-May I come in, my Sultan?
Come in.
Mighty Sultan, Valens the Lord of Bursa
wants to see you.
Make preparations. Leave now.
Politics is retaliation.
Now
Gather all the beggars in Konya
and bring them here.
Let's see if they need anything.
Lord of Bursa, sir...
Let the Lord of Bursa wait for a while, helper.
The Beys of tribes around
are coming as you ordered, mother.
We received news from Kopruhisar,
Bilecik and Inegol.
They all took precautions.
What about Yenisehir?
How are things in Yenisehir?
Measures have been increased.
We also placed patrol Alps around tribes.
My Allah, help us.
Stop..
You'll be alright.
My son..
Osman Bey, help us.
I will.
I will, I will. Don't worry.
Alps! Help everyone!
Are you alright?
-I am... I am...
-You'll be alright.
Aykurt, give her water!
Drink it.
Come here... You are alright, right?
I am alright. I am alright.
Dastards..
Look what they did to this tribe.
Don't worry, brother.
We'll make them pay for it, for sure.
Look at what they did to this tribe.
Look at what they did.
Look at those tents.
Dastards.
They did not attack walls or castles...
...they attacked the tribe,
which was easier for them to attack.
I swear, I will drown you in your blood.
My children..
My innocent children..
My innocent people...
Lord Valens.
You will heavily pay for this.
Cerkutay!
-Boran!
-My Bey.
Take Alps out!
You will meet people's needs.
You will treat everyone here!
-Yes my Bey.
Those Turks never forget anything.
They are also easily offended.
It's too weak for them to think
that your willpower can be broken...
...in this way, sir.
Let them get revenge.
When I really step on the battlefield...
...they will not have a palace to go.
Those people are blood thirsty.
They went back...
..but they won't stop.
But we will not stop as well.
We will not.
My children! -Osman.
Are you alright?
-Malhun.
-Osman.
We are alright, but...
-Are you alright?
-I am not.
Aktemur?
Alcicek?
Kumral Abdal, tell me.
What happened?
With Allah's consent,
he will heal and stand up, my Bey.
I hope he will.
Let me check them.
Thanks to Allah.
Aktemur..
Alcicek...
-Uncle.
-My son.
-Are you alright?
-Uncle...
I could not protect the entrustment, uncle.
They killed.
They killed people in front of me.
-I could not even die.
-My son...
How can you say that?
Does that suit a Bey?
You will be stronger than before.
So that they tried to kill us...
...now it is time to take their lives.
Turahan!
My Bey.
Call the Beys.
-I will gather the council.
-Yes my Bey.
Hadhrat Sultan..
Seeing you on the throne again
is such a big pleasure.
Congrats.
I appreciate, Lord Valens.
At the same time, I am mad.
I guess you are mad because
what happened on the frontiers.
You grieved the tribes of Turkmens.
And you are here, congratulating me.
Do not mistake me for someone else, Lord.
There is a difference between
the tribes and the Hadhrat Sultan.
This is one of the reasons of my visit.
Osman Bey is my enemy.
And I will kill him.
I want you to stop supporting him with your soldiers.
On those bloody lands,
one cannot get everything he wants...
..Lord Valens.
You are Gaznan Khan's..
-Adopted daughter.
If you allow me...
...I want to finish what I was saying to the Sultan.
Your Sultanate is quite new.
And Konya is fighting with poverty.
If Esrigun Hatun allows..
...Bursa wants to send
a large amount of supplies to Konya.
And the only thing necessary for that is...
...the preparation of the meeting
between me and Osman Bey.
Hadhrat Sultan.
Konya is dealing with poverty...
...and Osman Bey is dealing with you.
Lord.
We all want peace.
I will do the necessary thing.
He will arrange the meeting.
-Could you learn?
-I did, sir.
The army that is getting ready, the weapons, the catapults...
...those are all being sent to Osman.
What a shame...
He won't be able to send them.
Inform Nayman now.
Was that the Lord who allied with Nayman?
He was.
So snake Ismihan escaped again, huh?
She did. She escaped.
But she will not get away with this.
Thank Allah.
Ismihan left, the test is over, huh?
They always leave, my Ulgen.
But we are always being tested.
Turks are always being tested!
We still have that Lord!
We still have that Nayman or
whatever his name is!
I don't know what I am saying...
The souls of those who harm children...
...are dead inside!
Dead!
They will be their turn as well. Don't worry.
We won't stop until we take the lives of
those who hurt the poor.
Oh child, come..
Let me take you to your mother.
Malhun Hatun, are you alright?
Dark Midwife, my pain doesn't go away.
You didn't rest today.
May Allah protect you.
Look, you haven't done anything wrong,
did you?
When we were saying Sultan Mesut
sat on Konya throne..
And good news awaits us..
Bad news were awaiting us at tribe.
Don't worry though.
e will deal with them all.
Strengthen the flame in you.
When the aid from Sultan Mesut
comes to these lands..
We will make them pay.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
My Bey.
Even if the support arrives,
what can we do against Bursa's Lord?
Konur is right.
I wish revenge in every breath I take, Bey.
However..
Bursa is impassable.
What are we going to do, Bey?
We don't need to hit Bursa to hit its Lord.
The Lord is Byzantine itself.
And the closes Byzantine place is..
Kopruhisar.
They also use it as a stronghold to attack us.
If we take Kopruhisar..
Then we would deal great damage.
Lord Valens.
He already thinks about finishing us off.
However, he will break instead.
We will see..
After the support from Sultan arrives.
Are we allowed, Bey?
Come, Baysungur.
Bey.
Our scouts have sent word.
Tell me.
The aid, sent from Sultan..
Has been hit by Lord Vales and Nayman.
Nayman's Base
The future of these lands,
are in our hands now, Nayman.
Sultan Mesut's legions have been destroyed.
And Osman..
Osman is a dead man.
We will make a celebration in honor of this.
Servants.
The Lord of Kopruhisar,
my friend Petrus is also with us.
You have freed me and Kopruhisar,
from such a trouble..
Your arrival has been a grace.
Kopruhisar is free now, because of you.
You have teached those barbaric Turks their place.
Our alliance with Nayman..
Has become the end of Osman, Lord Petrus.
Osman is in a tight corner now.
I will put the collar on his neck.
I have plundered Osman's tribes.
Killed his people, his soldiers.
Osman can not move now.
That shepherd..
Has to compromise with us.
He will surrender.
I will make him my slave.
That is what they deserve, my Lord.
Slavery.
Then, as righteous winners..
We shall celebrate.
-With meat?
-Yes, meat.
-What will we do now, Bey?
-What do you think, Boran?
War needs support.
Ivaz Bey is right.
No aid means no war.
All those moves done in Konya
was going to provide us this benefit.
As you know..
Better than me as well..
However..
For war..
First, you need a heart to walk on that path.
In times like these..
Are we going to lose our hopes?
Osman Bey.
You command..
We will die not once,
but thousand times in your path.
What is your order, Bey?
They break our valiants..
Leave us scarred..
They want us to die..
By shooting aid coming from Sultan Mesut.
This is the greatest blow they did.
Why would they be scared of us?
Why would they hold back?
Bey, they inflicted many blows..
We need time to heal.
No.
The most dangerous wolf..
Is an injured wolf.
They do not expect us to make a move now.
Now, they are enjoying themselves
and waiting for us to die.
This is the right time to make a move.
Konur! Do you have the map of Kopruhisar
which we took in return for the ink?
I never left it Bey, in case we would need it.
-Nice. Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
They will face us with those big shields,
after passing the gates.
Inform all valiants ready the spears.
As you command, Bey.
Are we sure, Bey?
We are sure.
We are so sure about this.
We will move to the walls..
At the nightfall.
When all guards fall asleep...
We will attack.
As you command.
Thanks to Allah.
-Thank you, Soldiers! Attack!.
-Both of you are quite good.
Thanks to Allah.
But this stage is very important.
You know, Malhun Hatun.
You should protect both yourself and your baby.
You're right.
I had better be more careful.
Alright then. You take more rest.
And I'll go visit the healing tents.
Thank you, Dark Midwife
Dark Midwife.
Malhun.
-Are you alright?
-I'll give you some privacy, my Bey.
Malhun?
-My Osman...
-Malhun.
-Are you alright?
-I'm good.
My Osman..
During these dark times
...I've got great news.
Are you..
-Pregnant?
-I am.
Really? Is this real?
Praise be!
Amazing news it is!
Malhun.
Oh Malhun... Oh..
Thanks to Allah.
I got good news...
...and survived tough things.
But none of them...
...made me as happy as this did.
Thanks to Allah.
May Allah let us have a healthy baby.
Amen, my Osman. Amen.
May it put eternal delight in our hearts.
Now...
Another baby is coming, huh?
Then we can't fit in our lands.
We need new conquests.
Malhun.
Tonight, If Allah permits...
...we will conquer Kopruhisar.
If Allah permits, my Osman.
If Allah permits.
Don't forget what I said.
Keep your eyes on Sultan Mesut.
Watch his every moment and
every move and let me know.
And you will go to Bursa.
I want to know everything about Lord Valens.
Leave now.
Aral.
Get prepared, we will set out too.
Where will we go sir?
I'm not here for Konya alone,
I'm here in the name of the owner of all the lands.
We will go to Frontiers to Yenisehir.
Konur, there are four passages here.
You and infantries behind you will pass these passages.
When you sneak inside, you will shut the gate first.
So that soldiers cannot come towards us.
You will use the passages in the north.
Yes my Bey.
You will go this way, you know what to do.
Come on.
Boran and Cerkutay, you will come with me.
We will go to the Lord's room.
In secret, and silently.
They are sleeping peacefully out of joy as they hit us.
But we will wake them up with the sound of swords.
My Bey, if you permit, let me stay behind you.
Of course.
You're here to become our companion again,
Balaban, thank you.
Tell me, any news from the Lord?
Not yet, Bey.
And when they come,
they will find us instead, my Bey.
Exactly.
-Sir, guards are missing.
-They must've fallen asleep.
Light the candles.
Pull the soldiers back to the villages.
Osman is gone now.
He also doesn't have the power to fight.
He is too worn-out to come to Kopruhisar Castle.
Osman is done.
Welcome, dear Lord.
Drop it.
What are you doing in my castle?
You are now..
In my property.
Now what did you discuss..
With Nayman and Valens?
Did you...
Did you celebrate?
-W..we..
-Of course you did.
You definitely did.
You burnt down the tents.
Burnt down the villages.
Killed innocents.
And broke Osman's arms and legs and left him helpless.
You also attacked the supplies coming from Konya.
And Osman was left without a branch to hold on to.
You killed him, ended him..
Now look if he's dead.
Come here.
Get up.
Stand
Come here.
Come! Stand up!
Come here.. Stand up!
You killed many innocent people!
Come here...
Stand
Stand up! Stand up!
You won this time, Osman.
But... you...
-...and your generation...
-We will always be on these lands!
But your names will not even
be remembered in the future.
Your time has come.
Place the glorious flag of Kayi everywhere!
Tell everyone that Kopruhisar
is the property of Turks!
Tell the cruel..
...that Osman Bey is coming for them!
Allah is the greatest!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com